You know, I wish more of us cared about defending and supporting and rallying around political
prisoners, artists who make work for the purpose of empowering and elevating the oppressed,
uh, teachers, labor leaders, organizers. I wish more of us were interested in knowing who those
people are, platforming them, rallying around them, making sure that they're supported than we
are politicians. And I, I feel like if we did, then we would actually know in a much more
definitive way, the difference between a politician and a public servant.
I would argue that an elected official who's a public servant is there to create legislation
that supports and alleviates and fixes problems that actual people in the community are having to fix
on their own. You know, when these slaveholders founded this country, they didn't want people
to be career politicians. They wanted it to be like, you're doing like a civil service,
like you come in to be president or a congressperson, et cetera, et cetera. The same way that like folks
come in to do jury duty. Like it's something that you're doing because you're like, I actually think
I can improve things for us, for us, for us. And it's not that anymore because us is no longer
homogenous. And so now they're only doing work for them and not enough of us understand that yet.
So when you see me yelling, you see me talking, it's to, so it's to those of you who are still in
defense of a politician. And I will continue to yell and I will continue to talk and I will continue
to sing until the day that I die. If it means that more people will understand what they deserve
and from whom. And as we find ourselves in the midst of Black August, we must remember to center,
to learn from, to remember, and to elevate those who have lost their lives and their freedom
in pursuit of collective liberation.
Gerard, so you should name that.